[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "The first paragraph indicates that the article uses butterflies to discuss the effects of climate change.",
        "answer": "true"
    },
    {
        "question": "The article begins with which of the following?",
        "answer": "a quote"
    },
    {
        "question": "Paragraph two mentions an “insect apocalypse.” Which of the following best describes this phrase?",
        "answer": "a negative event with many insect species dying"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, the west coast of the U.S. ___ each year.",
        "answer": "loses slightly less than two percent of its butterfly population"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following butterfly species was directly mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "the Western Monarch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on the article, which of the following is a major problem related to declining insect populations?",
        "answer": "rising temperatures due to climate change"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, Taiwan _____ .",
        "answer": "once sold more butterfly wings than any country in the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most likely reason the writer chose to add a question to the first and final paragraphs?",
        "answer": "Both paragraphs ask a question to get the reader’s attention and to show that the article was ending in the same style that it began."
    },
    {
        "question": "Paragraph two mentions “global insect populations steadily dropping.” Which of the following best describes this phrase?",
        "answer": "a negative event with many insect species dying"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the article, which area of the U.S. has experienced a butterfly decrease?",
        "answer": "the west coast"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do the first and final paragraphs of the article have in common?",
        "answer": "They both ask a question to get the reader’s attention."
    },
    {
        "question": "The first paragraph indicates that the article’s topic is climate change and human population growth.",
        "answer": "false"
    },
    {
        "question": "Paragraph two mentions two studies related to an “insect apocalypse,” with one study examining specific butterfly populations and another study examining general insect populations. Which of the studies was smaller?",
        "answer": "the U.S. west coast butterfly population study"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first paragraph of the article ends with which of the following?",
        "answer": "a question"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the end of the first paragraph, what does the word “it” refer to?",
        "answer": "nature’s message"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following were NOT mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "the 1960s"
    },
    {
        "question": "Paragraph two mentions two studies related to an “insect apocalypse,” with one study examining specific butterfly populations and another study examining general insect populations. Which of the studies was bigger?",
        "answer": "the global insect population study"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the beginning of the first paragraph, what does the word “it” refer to?",
        "answer": "nature’s message"
    }
]